Guide to the M. Moran Weston Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VII: Housing
  - National Association for Affordable Housing, Inc. Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 87, Folder 510)
  - Housing for People, Inc. Correspondence (Box 87, Folder 511)
  - National Association for Affordable Housing, Inc. Correspondence, memos., documents, etc. 1882-1987, (5 folders) (Box 87, Folder 512-516)
  - National Association for Affordable Housing, Inc. Correspondence, memos., documents, etc. 1988, (4 folders) (Box 88, Folder 517-520)
  - National Association for Affordable Housing, Inc. Correspondence, memos., documents, etc. 1989, (4 folders) (Box 89, Folder 521-524)
  - National Association for Affordable Housing, Inc. Correspondence, memos., documents, etc. 1988 and 1989, (5 folders) (Box 90, Folder 525-529)
  - National Association for Affordable Housing, Inc. Correspondence, memos., documents, etc. 1988 and 1989, (7 folders) (Box 91, Folder 530-536)
  - National Association for Affordable Housing, Inc. Correspondence, memos., documents, etc. 1990-1993, (7 folders) (Box 92, Folder 537-543)
  - National Association for Affordable Housing, Inc. Correspondence, accounts, bills, etc. 1989-1993, (12 folders) (Box 93, Folder 544-555)
- Series VIII: Harlem Development Projects
  - Urban Ventures, Inc. Correspondence, accounts, bills, etc. 1969-1985, (8 folders) (Box 94, Folder 556-563)
  - Harlem on the Hudson Correspondence, accounts, bills, etc. 1964-1989, (11 folders) (Box 95, Folder 564-574)
  - Harlem on the Hudson Correspondence, accounts, bills, etc. 1971-1973 (Box 96, Folder 575 & 576)
  - Saint Nicholas Park Community Council, Inc. Correspondence, accounts, bills, etc. 1967-1971 (Box 96, Folder 577)
  - Urban Associates Clippings, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 578)
  - Urban affairs. Prince: 101 Park Ave. 1969 (Box 96, Folder 579)
  - Urban Associates Clippings, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 580)
  - Urban Ventures Accounts, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 581)
  - Housing for People, Inc. RFP [Request for Proposals] for site at 135th Street abd St. Nicholas Avenue, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 582)
  - St. Philip's Church St. Nicholas Urban Renewal Area correspondence memos documents etc., 1966-1979 (Box 97, Folder 583-587)
  - Central Harlem Plaza Corridor Correspondence, memos., plans, exhibits, etc., 1979-1987 (Box 98, Folder 588 & 589)
  - Central Harlem Plaza Corridor Correspondence, memos., plans, exhibits, etc., [New York], 1971-1980 (Box 99, Folder 590-594)
  - Seabury House Papers, 1950 (Box 173, Folder 953)
- Series IX: Carver Savings And Loans
  - Carver Federal Savings and Loan Association Statements, correspondence, clippings, etc. 1970-1989 (Box 100, Folder 595-601)
  - Carver Federal Savings and Loan Association Statements, correspondence, clippings, etc. 1950-1987 (Box 101, Folder 602-607)
  - Carver Federal Savings and Loan Association General correspondence, [n.d.] and 1988-1991 (Box 102, Folder 608-612)
  - Carver Federal Savings and Loan Association General correspondence, 1992 and 1993 (Box 103, Folder 613-616)
  - Carver Federal Savings and Loan Association General correspondence, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 617-619)
  - Carver Federal Savings and Loan Association General correspondence, 1993 (Box 105, Folder 620-622)
  - Carver Federal Savings and Loan Association General correspondence, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 623-625)
  - Carver Federal Savings and Loan Association General correspondence, 1994 and 1995 (Box 107, Folder 626-628)
  - Carver Federal Savings and Loan Association General correspondence, 1995 and 1996 (Box 108, Folder 629-630)
- Series X: Boards of Directors and Committees
  - CARE Correspondence, reports, memos., etc. 1982-1992, (4 folders) (Box 109, Folder 631; 634-636)
  - American Red Cros Corerspondence, minutes, etc. 1979 (Box 109, Folder 632)
  - New York State. Board of Public Disclosure Correspondenc and minutes, 1981 and 1982 (Box 109, Folder 633)
  - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, Inc. Correspondence, minutes, etc. 1993 (Box 110, Folder 637)
  - New York City Mission Society Correspondence, minutes, etc. 1960 and 1961 (Box 110, Folder 638)
  - CARE Correspondence, minutes, etc. 1985-1990 (Box 110, Folder 639 & 640)
  - Cathedral of St. John the Divine. Board of Trustees Correspondence, reports, statements, etc. 1983 and 1984 (Box 110, Folder 641)
  - Child Adoption Service. Board of Directors Correspondence, 1962 (Box 110, Folder 642)
  - Cildren's Aid Society Correspondence, 1967 (Box 110, Folder 643)
  - Children's Defense Fund Clipping, 1980 (Box 110, Folder 644)
  - Citizen's Committee on the Problems of Alcohol Letter, 12 May 1969 (Box 110, Folder 645)
  - Coalition for Higher Education Letter and statement, 1980 (Box 110, Folder 646)
  - The Association the the Bar of the City of New York. Committee on Grievances Correspondence, etc. 1977-1979 (Box 110, Folder 647)
  - Community Council of Greater New York. Board of Directors Correspondence, etc. 1959-1967 (Box 110, Folder 648)
  - Council for Religion in Public Schools Correspondence, etc. 1961-1967 (Box 110, Folder 649)
  - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies Letter, 22 March 1966 (Box 110, Folder 650)
  - Foreign Policy Association Correspondence, etc. 1980-1989 (Box 111, Folder 651)
  - Girl Scouts of the United States of America Correspondence, etc. 1959 and 1960 (Box 111, Folder 652)
  - Harlem Neighborhoods Association, Inc. Correspondence, etc. 1959 (Box 111, Folder 653)
  - Harlem Neighborhoods Association, Inc. Correspondence, etc. 1961 and 1962 (Box 111, Folder 654)
  - Harlem Cultural Council Correspondence, etc. 1978 (Box 111, Folder 655)
  - Helath Services Aency Correspondence, etc. 1978 (Box 111, Folder 656)
  - IBOS [Independent Black Opera Singers], Inc. Correspondence, etc. 1980 (Box 111, Folder 657)
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ in the United States of America Correspondence, etc. 1961 (Box 111, Folder 658)
  - Sarah R. Numan Nursing Home Correspondence, etc. 1992 (Box 112, Folder 659)
  - New York City Mission Society. Board of Directors Correspondence, etc. 1962 (Box 112, Folder 660)
  - SUNY. African-American Institute Correspondence, etc. 1986 (Box 112, Folder 661)
  - New York Voluntary Enterprise Commission Correspondence, etc. 1985 (Box 112, Folder 662)
  - Phelps-Stokes Fund Correspondence, etc. 1972-1980 (Box 112, Folder 663-667)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City Correspondence, leaflets, etc. (Box 113, Folder 668)
  - The Schomburg Commission (Schomburg Center for Research in Black Culture) Correspondence, leaflets, etc. (Box 113, Folder 669)
  - State Commission for Human Rights, Citizens Committee Correspondence, etc. (Box 113, Folder 670)
  - Tri-Continental Association Correspondence, etc. 1978 (Box 113, Folder 671)
  - Tri-Continental Association Correspondence, etc. 1979 - 1986 (Box 113, Folder 672)
  - United Way Annual Report, correspondence, etc. (Box 113, Folder 673)
  - Urban League of Westchester County Annual Fellowship Dinner -- Programs, Correspondence, etc. (Box 113, Folder 674)
  - Channel Thirteen Community Advisory Board Meeting Agenda, minutes, correspondence, etc. (Box 113, Folder 675)
  - Westchester Coalition, Inc. Annual Reports, minutes, calender, etc. (Box 113, Folder 676)
  - Roy Wilkins Foundation Correspondence, leaflets, etc. (Box 113, Folder 677)
  - Sovern Investiture Transparencies, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 678)
  - Sovern Investiture Transparencies, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 679)
  - Columbia University - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1969 - 1978 (Box 114, Folder 680)
  - Columbia University - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1979 (Box 114, Folder 681)
  - Columbia University - Board of Trustees Correspondence, January - September 1980 (Box 114, Folder 682)
  - Columbia University - Board of Trustees Correspondence, October - December 1980 (Box 114, Folder 683)
  - Columbia University - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1981 (Box 114, Folder 684)
  - Columbia University - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 685)
  - Columbia University - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1983 - 1986 (Box 115, Folder 686)
  - Columbia University - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1987 - (Box 115, Folder 687)
  - Columbia University Events (Other than trustee meetings) leaflets etc. 1976 - 1979 (Box 115, Folder 688)
  - Columbia University. Board of Trustees Newspaper clippings (Box 115, Folder 689)
  - Columbia University Events (Other than trustee meetings) correspondence leaflets etc. 1980 - 1989 (Box 115, Folder 690)
  - Columbia University. Doctor of Sacred Theology. Honoris Causa, 1969 (Box 115, Folder 691)
  - Columbia Commencement Photos of M. Moran Weston, 1971 (Box 115, Folder 692)
  - Columbia University - Board of Trustees Confidential Papers (Box 115, Folder 693)
  - Community Service Council Correspondence & Papers (Box 116, Folder 694)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center, Inc. Confidential Papers (Box 116, Folder 695)
  - Mount Sinai Board of Trutees Business Correspondence, 1970 - 1981 (Box 116, Folder 696-699)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center Business Correspondence, Annual Reports, etc. 1982 - 1992 (Box 116, Folder 700-701)
  - NAACP Legal Defense Fund Correspondence, Papers, Leaflets, etc. 1965 - 1988 (Box 117, Folder 702-706)
  - NAACP Legal Defense Fund Correspondence, papers, leaflets, etc. 1989 - 1993 (Box 118, Folder 707-709)
  - Saint Augustine's College. Board of Trustees Correspondence, papers, leaflets, etc. 1962 - 1977 (Box 119, Folder 710-713)
  - Saint Augustine's College. Board of Trustees Correspondence, papers, leaflets, etc. 1977 - 1980 (Box 120, Folder 714-718)
  - Saint Augustine's College. Board of Trustees Correspondence, papers, leaflets, etc. 1981 - 1984 (Box 121, Folder 719-721)
  - Saint Augustine's College. Board of Trustees Correspondence, papers, leaflets, etc. 1985-1989 (Box 122, Folder 722-726)
  - Saint Augustine's College. Board of Trustees Correspondence, papers, leaflets, etc. 1990-1996 (Box 123, Folder 727-730)
  - Saint Augustine's College. Board of Trustees Correspondence, papers, leaflets, etc. 1985 (Box 124, Folder 731-733)
  - Committee on Grievances of the New York Bar Association Confidential - Correspondence Agenda Papers Minutes etc. (Box 171, Folder 946)
  - Urban League of Westchester Correspondence Papers etc. (Box 173, Folder 956)
- Series XI: Sermons, Speeches and Invocations
  - Saint Philip's Sermons and ideas for sermons, 1958-1985 (Box 125, Folder 734-739)
  - Saint Philip's Sermons and ideas for sermons, 1961 and 1962 (Box 126, Folder 740-742)
  - Saint Philip's Sermons and ideas for sermons, 1963-1966 (Box 127, Folder 743-747)
  - Saint Philip's Sermons and ideas for sermons, 1967-1974 (Box 128, Folder 747a-754)
  - Saint Philip's Sermons and ideas for sermons, 1975-1977 (Box 129, Folder 755-759)
  - Saint Philip's Sermons and ideas for sermons, 1978 and 1979 (Box 130, Folder 760-763)
  - Saint Philip's Sermons and ideas for sermons, 1980 and 1981 (Box 131, Folder 764-767)
  - Saint Philip's Intercessions, 1968 (Box 131, Folder 768)
  - Saint Philip's Other ministers at St. Philip's, 1962-1971 (Box 131, Folder 769)
  - Saint Philip's Other ministers at St. Philip's, 1977 (Box 132, Folder 770)
  - Saint Philip's Sermons and ideas for sermons, 1982 & 1983 (Box 132, Folder 771-773)
  - Saint Philip's Sermons and ideas for sermons, 1950-1957 (Box 133, Folder 774-779)
  - Saint Philip's Bulletins, 1957-1980 (Box 133, Folder 780)
  - Saint Philip's Music at the church, 1974-1979 (Box 133, Folder 781)
  - Sermons, Invocations and Speeches, [n.d.] & 1930-1960 (Box 134, Folder 782-786)
  - Sermons, Invocations and Speeches, 1960-1963 (Box 135, Folder 787-792)
  - Sermons, Invocations and Speeches, 1964 and 1965 (Box 136, Folder 793-797)
  - Sermons, Invocations and Speeches, 1965-1980 (Box 137, Folder 798-804)
  - Sermons and speeches by others, [n.d.] (Box 137, Folder 805)
  - Speeches and invocations, 1977-1987 (Box 138, Folder 806 & 807)
  - Resources for speeches, [n.d.] and 1954 (Box 139, Folder 808-812)
  - Sermon scrapbook, 1953-1955 (Box 139, Folder 813)
- Series XII: Manuscripts and Publications
  - Columbia University dissertation proposal, 1952 (Box 140, Folder 814)
  - Columbia University dissertation chapter IV, 1952 (Box 140, Folder 815)
  - Correspondence relating to the publication of Social Policy of the Episcopal Church in the Twentieth Century, 1963 and 1964 (Box 140, Folder 816)
  - Social Policy of the Episcopal Church in the Twentieth Century. Copy of original dissertation as well as the published book. [n.d.] and 1964, (2 bound volumes) (Box 140)
  - Columbia senior theses, 1929/30 (Box 141, Folder 817)
  - Weston, Milton M. Writings (Box 141, Folder 818)
  - Filing guide (Box 141, Folder 819)
  - West 135th Street affair, 1977 (Box 141, Folder 820)
  - Inner City Scholarship Fund, Inc. Correspondence and manuscript, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 821)
  - The Black Church. UTS textbook or course, 1959 (Box 141, Folder 822)
  - Articles and essays by various authors. (Box 141, Folder 823-852)
  - Poetry of Protest. Manuscript. (Box 142, Folder 853)
  - Various published works by Weston. (Box 142, Folder 854)
  - Letters to the Editor by Weston. (Box 142, Folder 855)
  - "We Are One." Proposal for the developement of a television series of interviews with Weston. (Box 142, Folder 856)
  - At the Edge of a New Age: The Age of Man. Manuscript. (Box 142, Folder 857)
  - Before the Thunder. Manuscript. (Box 142, Folder 858)
  - Various plans for publications. (Box 142, Folder 859)
  - Books by Weston. (Box 142, Folder 860)
  - Africa and the African Diaspora. Manuscript. (Box 142, Folder 861)
  - Publications by Weston. (Box 142, Folder 862)
  - Correspondence and manuscripts. (Box 142, Folder 863)
  - Weston manuscripts. (Box 142, Folder 864)
  - Newspapers clippings., 1943-1945, (3 volumes) (Box 143)
  - "The New Yorker" Magazine Article - "That Was New York - Harlem" (Box 174, Folder 967)
- Series XIII: Teaching
  - SUNY Albany General correspondence, [n.d.] and 1968-1973 (Box 144, Folder 865-870)
  - SUNY Albany General correspondence, 1974-1981 (Box 145, Folder 871-874)
  - SUNY Albany Prof. Weston's personal correspondence, 1969-1974 (Box 146, Folder 875 & 876)
  - SUNY Albany Plans for an Environmental Studies Program (Box 146, Folder 877)
  - Black Academy of Arts and Letters Correspondence, 1972 (Box 147, Folder 878)
  - SUNYA Journal, 1987 (Box 147, Folder 880)
  - SUNY Albany. African American Studies Department Correspondence, 1969 and 1970 (Box 147, Folder 881-885)
  - SUNY Albany. African American Studies Department Correspondence relating to the Holte Collection, 1969 (Box 147, Folder 886)
  - SUNY Albany. African American Studies Department Class notes (Box 148, Folder 887 & 888)
  - SUNY Albany. African American Studies Department Syllabi and course materials, 1969-1977 (Box 148, Folder 889-893)
  - SUNY Albany. African American Studies Department Syllabi and course materials as well as materials from other professors, 1969-1977 (Box 149, Folder 894-901)
  - SUNY Albany. African American Studies Department Syllabi and course materials on the Black family, 1970-1976 (Box 150, Folder 902-905)
  - State University of New York, Albany Correspondence with Students, 1971 - 1972 (Box 166, Folder 928)
  - State University of New York, Albany Course on Social Problems in Black Community (AAS 333) - Student Papers, Summer 1972 (Box 166, Folder 929)
  - State University of New York, Albany Course on The Black Family (AAS 331) - Student Papers, Fall 1973 (Box 166, Folder 930)
  - State University of New York, Albany The Black Family (AAS 331) - Student Papers, Fall 1974 (Box 166, Folder 931)
  - State University of New York, Albany The Black Family - Student Papers, Spring 1975 (Box 166, Folder 932)
  - State University of New York, Albany The Black Family - Student Papers, Fall 1975 (Box 166, Folder 933)
  - State University of New York, Albany Black Religion, Spring 1976 (Box 166, Folder 934)
  - State University of New York, Albany Student Papers (Box 167, Folder 935)
  - State University of New York, Albany Course on The Black Religion (AAS 141 AAS 341), Fall 1969 (Box 167, Folder 936)
  - State University of New York, Albany The Black Family - Student Papers, Fall 1970 (Box 167, Folder 937)
  - State University of New York, Albany The Black Family - Student Papers, Spring 1971 (Box 167, Folder 938)
  - State University of New York, Albany The Black Family - Student Papers, Fall 1971 (Box 167, Folder 939)
  - State University of New York, Albany Afro-American Studies 333 - Student Exams, Fall 1971 (Box 167, Folder 940)
  - State University of New York, Albany The Black Family - Student Papers, Spring 1972 (Box 167, Folder 941)
  - State University of New York, Albany Afro-American Studies 333 - Student Papers, Spring 1972 (Box 167, Folder 942)
  - SUNY Albany. African American Studies Department Graduate programs, [n.d.] and 1969-1971 (Box 151, Folder 906-908)
  - SUNY Albany. African American Studies Department Black Family Research Project [oral histories] (Box 153, Folder 914-917)
  - SUNY Albany. African American Studies Department Black Family Research Project [General Materials including correspondence] (Box 152, Folder 909)
  - SUNY Albany. African American Studies Department Family Research Instruments (Box 152, Folder 910)
  - SUNY Albany. African American Studies Department Oral History Project [Family Trees etc.] (Box 152, Folder 911)
  - SUNY Albany. African American Studies Department Oral Histories (Box 152, Folder 912)
  - SUNY Albany. African American Studies Department Black Family Research Project. Oral Histories (Box 152, Folder 913)
  - University of Ife, Nigeria Correspondence, manuscripts, etc. 1977-1979 (Box 154, Folder 918-923)
  - State University of New York, Albany Personal Papers (Box 171, Folder 943)
  - State University of New York, Albany Confidential - Search For Academic VP (Box 171, Folder 945)
  - State University of New York, Albany Student Grades and Correspondences (Box 172, Folder 947)
- Series XIV: Cataloged Correspondence
  - Abernathy, Ralph To Friend of Freedom, Atlanta, GA, 25 May 1959, (1 t.l.s. (mimeograph)) (Box 155)
  - Anderson, Marian To M. Moran Weston, Danbury, CT, 15 November 1962, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Astor, Brooke To M. Moran Weston, New York, NY, 10 April 1992, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Bailey, Pearl To M. Moran Weston, New York, NY, 19 March 1970, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Davis, Ossie To M. Moran Weston, New York, NY, [n.d.]; 6 December 1978 and 24 November 1981, (1 t.l.s., 2 a.l.s., 1 signed order of service) (Box 155)
  - Dee, Ruby To M. Moran Weston, New York, NY, 2 November 1992 and 10 Februray 1993, (2 a.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Delaney, Sadie and Bessie To M. Moran Weston, Mount Vernon, NY, 7 February and 17 March 1961, (2 a.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Dinkins, David N. To M. Moran Weston, New York, NY, 21 December 1988 and 24 July 1991, (2 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Edelman, Marian Wright To M. Moran Weston, [n.p.] and Washington, DC, 9 March 1962 - 31 October 1980, (2 a.l.s., 1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Fauset, Arthur H. To M. Moran Weston, New York, NY, 1 October 1968, (1 a.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Fax, Elton To M. Moran Weston, Long Island City, NY, 13 July 1987, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Franklin, John Hope To M. Moran Weston, Durham, NC, 16 April 1993, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Higginbotham, A. Leon To M. Moran Weston, Philadelphia, PA, 21 April 1992, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Hoving, Thomas P. To M. Moran Weston, New York, NY, 13 September 1968, (1 t.l.s., 2 pages) (Box 155)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H. To M. Moran Weston, Washington, DC, 11 July 1968, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Jordan, Vernon E. To M. Moran Weston, New York, NY, 19 October 1977, (1 t.n.s.) (Box 155)
  - Kennedy, Robert F. To M. Moran Weston, Washington, DC, 22 July 1966 and 19 January 1968, (2 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - King, Coretta Scott To M. Moran Weston, Atlanta, GA, 3 September 1968, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Koch, Edward I To M. Moran Weston, New York, NY, 5 July 1978 - 9 August 1985, (4 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Lindsay, John V. To M. Moran Weston, New York, NY, 15 September 1966, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - McCall, Carl To M. Moran Weston, New York and Albany, NY, 26 September 1977 and 12 October 1982, (2 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Mitchell, Lofton To M. Moran Weston, Johnson City, NY, 7 February 1977, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Morrison, Toni To M. Moran Weston, New York, NY, 17 October 1977, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Motley, Constance Baker To M. Moran Weston, New York, NY, 11 July 1966, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - O'Neal, Frederick To M. Moran Weston, New York, NY, 7 February 1989, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Osofsky, Gilbert To M. Moran Weston, New York, NY, ca. 9 November 1962, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Powell, Adam Clayton To M. Moran Weston, New York & Washington, DC, 2 June 1950 & 18 July 1969, (2 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Randolph, A. Philip To M. Moran Weston, New York, 29 November 1961 & 8 March 1962, (2 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Rangel, Charles B. To M. Moran Weston, Washington, DC, 11 March 1992, (1 a.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Robinson, Jackie To M. Moran Weston, New York, 15 May 1961, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. To M. Moran Weston, New York, 5 March 1979, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. To M. Moran Weston, Albany, 15 May 1962 - 18 July 1968, (3 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Runcie, Robert To M. Moran Weston, St. Albans, Herts, 9 July 1993, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Rustin, Bayard To M. Moran Weston, New York, 14 April & 4 August 1987, (2 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Schuyler, George S. To M. Moran Weston, New York, 21 October 1962, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Sutton, Percy To M. Moran Weston, New York, 30 September 1966 and 4 May 1977, (2 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Tutu, Desmond To M. Moran Weston, Claremont Cape, South Africa, 9 January 1987, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Van Vechten, Carl To M. Moran Weston, New York, NY, 20 July 1961, (1 t.l.s.) (Box 155)
  - Wright, Marian E. To M. Moran Weston, Yale, CT, 23 September 1961, (1 a.l.s., 4 pages) (Box 155)
  - Watts, Andre Signed concert program, NC, 1976 (Box 155)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and carbons, [v.p.], [v.d.], (23 letters) (Box 155, Folder 924)
- Series XV: Photographs
  - Weston, Nola Jeanne Album of photographs, [n.p.], [n.d.], (1 volume) (Box 156)
  - Photographs of M. Moran Weston St. Philip's Church and notable visitors, New York, [v.d.], (ca. 300 photographs) (Box 157 & 158)
  - Photographs of Annual Fellowship Luncheons; 135th Street Houses; Upper Manhattan Day Care and Child delelopement Center; Community Youth Center; Miscellaneous people, New York, [v.d.], (ca. 150 photographs) (Box 159)
- Series XVI: Film, Audiotapes and Casettes
  - "Lindsay at St. Phillip's Church Luncheon", New York, [n.d.], (1 reel of film) (Box 160)
  - Weston, M. Moran Sermons, 1960s, (4 reels of audio tape) (Box 160)
  - Weston, M. Moran Sermons and speeches, New York, 1971-1982, (43 cassette tapes) (Box 161)
  - St. Philip's Church Programs of service, New York, 1965 - 1966 (Box 162, Folder 925)
  - St. Philip's Church Easter, New York, 1964, (1 motion picture reel (16mm)) (Box 162, Folder 926)
  - St. Philip's Church Service and sermons, New York, 1963-1968, (9 reels of audio tape) (Box 162)
  - Weston, M. Moran Sermons, New York, [v.d.], (43 audio cassettes) (Box 163)
  - Weston, M. Moran Sermons, New York, [v.d.], (43 audio cassettes) (Box 163A)
  - Weston, M. Moran Sermons, New York, [v.d.], (43 audio cassettes) (Box 163B)
  - Weston, M. Moran Sermons, New York, [v.d.], (43 audio cassettes) (Box 163C)
  - Dr. Moran M. Weston Sermons and Speeches, 1968- 1969, (4 Audio Recording Tapes) (Box 164)
  - Dr. Moran M. Weston St. Philip's Church Programs of service, New York, 1967 - 1969 (Box 164, Folder 927)
  - M. Moran Weston Sermons and speeches, (2 Audio Tapes) (Box 173, Folder 952)